Inventory of Half a Century of Communist Cadre Training records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Supporting Documents, 1966-1972 (Boxes 3-18)
  - Numerical file of prospective participants, 1967-1972
    - No. 337. Gregori Rostvorov (Box-folder 16: 41)
    - No. 338. Junius Scales (Box-folder 16: 42)
    - No. 339. Sejna (Box-folder 16: 43)
    - No. 340. Max Shachtman (Box-folder 16: 44)
    - No. 342. Barzillat (Box-folder 16: 45)
    - No. 343. Ales Bebler (Box-folder 16: 46)
    - No. 344. Berger (Box-folder 16: 47)
    - No. 345. Sydney Dark (Box-folder 16: 48)
    - No. 346. Dobos (Box-folder 16: 49)
    - No. 348. Peter Fryer (Box-folder 16: 50)
    - No. 349. Yurij Gustincic (Box-folder 16: 51)
    - No. 350. Emanuel John Hevi (Box-folder 16: 52)
    - No. 351. Douglas Hyde (Box-folder 16: 53)
    - No. 352. Willi Münzenberg (Box-folder 16: 54)
    - No. 353. Mrs. Heinz Neumann (Box-folder 16: 55)
    - No. 355. Roarvo Tuomen (Box-folder 16: 56)
    - No. 356. Velebit (Box-folder 16: 57)
    - No. 383-385. Dead ends (Box-folder 16: 58)
  - Logistical correspondence, memoranda, notes, lists, and informational handouts during conference, 1969 (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Press coverage of conference, 1969 (Box-folder 17: 2)
  - Post-conference correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 17: 3)
    Mainly responses to press coverage
  - Post-conference papers submitted
    - Greig, Ian, "Background Notes on Militant Groups in British Schools,", circa 1969 (Box-folder 17: 4)
      Typescript
    - Raymond, Edward A., "Education of Foreigners in the Soviet Union,", 1970 (Box-folder 17: 5)
    - Editorial correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 17: 6)
      Relates to planned publication of conference papers. Includes correspondence with Edward T. Barnard, Doubleday and Company, and University of South Carolina Press; and background questionnaires and format specifications for authors
    - Miscellany, 1967-1969, undated (Box-folder 18: 1)
      Notes, fragments, and printed matter
    - Computer disks of hard-copy documents and comparative and statistical data derived from them (Box-folder 18: 2)
- Sound Recordings (Box 19)
  Sound recordings on twenty-nine 7 inch reels that likely contain the original conference recordings, for which there are transcripts in the Proceedings series.